Komish you got listen to me. Oh no now one more comment from you. I'm done rebasing your mistakes
You're on junior CSS duty until further notice. Komish you can't do this to me
Keep talking and you'll be doing store procedures for a month now get out of gear. Take him with you
Fun fact CSS is actually touring complete
Larry Gary Tango Mary. I just pull in your request. It looks good to me. You're
clear to ship. Thanks. You're welcome. Next. It's an awfully big PR. For an intern. Well I just
bumped some dependencies. It's nothing major. Hey can I get a quick stamp on this? Yeah
I don't worry about it. Quick approval. Not on my watch. I'm on your diff like a
Pete has on side. Not this again. It's literally just a hex code change. Just a
prove it. Just a prove it. Squish per persisting review. Oh I know you're the
tip where I've seen five coding but that ain't it. I hate merge cop. He always makes
reviewing take forever. We have code rabbit. Oh come on. I wasn't even merging the
prod. It was a hex code change. We have code rabbit. We don't need real
people reviewing such simple changes. Code rabbit can do it for us. Our engineer's
time is better spent solving problems for customers. You can try it too at
code rabbit dot AI. Next week on merge cop. Now my plan to merge it so big. You're the
tip where and I always knew it.